http://www.bluetie.com/legal/privacy-policy/

Contact Us Today!
Contact Us
(0)
Item Added to Cart!
Your cart is empty!
1. General
BlueTie respects the privacy of every individual who visits www.bluetie.com (the "Web Site" or "Site"). This Privacy Policy outlines the information we will collect and how we will use and share that information. This Policy will also tell you what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared. If you have any questions about our policy, you may contact us by email.
2. Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using the Web Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Site. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to its terms means you accept those changes.
3. Personally-Identifiable Information
There are cases where we may ask you for personally-identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, email address and telephone number. We request personally-identifiable information when you register as a member of the Web Site, for online transactions, feedback forms, surveys and for other services that require registration or subscription. We will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. Please note that although certain registrations within BlueTie require certain user information, registration itself is entirely optional. We will also collect other users’ comments about you in our feedback area.
When you provide us with personally-identifiable information, BlueTie may:
store and process that information to better understand your needs, customize your experience, and to improve our products and services;
use that information to contact you periodically via email and postal mail for informational purposes (i.e. site updates, system outages, etc.);
disclose that information to third parties who need such information to provide products and services that you have requested;
disclose that information to third parties when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
4. Non-Personally-Identifiable Information
BlueTie may also collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. This type of information includes your age, gender, zip code, area code, interests and preferences. We will not collect any such information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. We may share this information in the aggregate with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. For example, we may inform a sponsor that the membership of the Web Site is x percent females and y percent males. These data are used to customize our Site’s content and advertising. We will also use that and other data and information to make visits to the Site easier, quicker, and better for you and our other members and users. We also may track certain information about your visit to the Web Site, including (without limitation) pages viewed, clickstreams, and searches. Such information is gathered in the aggregate and is not identified by any specific users.
5. Other Special Circumstances
Contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions on the Site will have separate privacy practices with regard to the information collected in connection with entering or participating in any such event. You will have a choice of whether or not you would like to allow certain information shared with third parties who may have a product or service of interest to you. You will also have the choice of whether a company that is co-sponsoring a promotion or contest may contact or send information to you.
6. Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
7. Information Collected Automatically
BlueTie may also automatically collect non-personally-identifiable information about your use of the Web Site, such as the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account), the date and time you access the Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Site. This information will not be linked to personally-identifiable information. We may use this information to analyze and enhance our Web Site and for security purposes, and we may aggregate this information and share the aggregated information with business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.
8. Information Placed Automatically On Your Computer’s Hard Drive
Not all cookies are edible. A "cookie" is information stored on your computer when you view a website. Our cookies help us in many ways. For example, a cookie is used to remember your username (if desired). This means that the next time you log in to BlueTie, you will only have to enter your password. If you visit another website from our Site, you may also receive a cookie or similar file from that site. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. Remember, however, that blocking or deleting cookies may limit your ability to access some or all of the features and services of the Web Site.
9. Uploaded Information
We will not disclose to third parties any information, data and other materials that you upload to any non-public areas of the service offered on the Web Site (e.g., your calendar, your file folders, etc.) except as directed by you or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
10. Changing or Deleting Your Personal Information
BlueTie allows you to modify or delete your personal information or preferences, by clicking on the “Edit My Info” link in the top right corner of the navigation. You may also call BlueTie at 1-800-BLUE-TIE to request account cancellations or information changes.
11. Children
The Web Site is not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age, and BlueTie does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals.
12. Links to Other Websites
The Web Site allows links to various other web sites. We assume no responsibility for the information practices of sites you are able to access through the Web Site. Furthermore, a link to another does not imply an affiliation or an endorsement of that linked site.
13. Data Security and Integrity
Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online — for example, via instant messaging or online meetings— that information can be collected and used by people you don’t know. While BlueTie strives to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk.
The importance of security for all personally-identifiable information associated with our users and members is of utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally-identifiable information, we can’t ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. However, once we receive your personally-identifiable information, we will take reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
In certain areas BlueTie uses SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
Your account on the Web Site is password protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. BlueTie will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Remember to sign out of your account on the Web Site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This will ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others, if you share a computer with someone else, or if you use a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafè.
14. Data Sharing and Disclosure
Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Our Rights
We may, in certain situations, be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to comply with or meet national security or law enforcement requirements.  We may disclose personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process to establish or excise our legal rights, or to defend against legal claims.  We may also share personal information if we believe it is necessary in the investigation of, or to prevent illegal activities, fraud, potential threats to the physical safety of any person, the protection of minors, violations of our Service Agreement, or otherwise required by law.
Third Party Service Providers
We may share information, including personal information, with our approved third-party service providers that we use for Services delivery such as archiving, backups, encryption, customer relationship systems and other services.  Approved third-party services may have access to your personal information for the purposes of providing these services.  BlueTie does not permit the use of your personal information by third-parties for the purposes of marketing or for any other purpose other than the intended purpose of the service they provide to BlueTie.
Client Testimonials
We may post testimonials on our Websites or other websites, or in connection with advertising our Services that may contain personal information.  We will obtain written consent to post your name, along with the testimonial.  If you wish to update your information, or withdraw your consent, contact privacy@bluetie.com.
With Consent
For all other purposes not explicitly stated above, we may request your consent to share your personal information.
Legal Basis For Processing (European Economic Area Only)
BlueTie’s legal basis for collecting and utilizing personally identifiable information of Individuals from the European Economic Area (EEA) will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which the information is collected.  We will normally collect personal information from you where (a) you have provided your consent to do so, (b) we need the personal information to deliver BlueTie Services, (c) we have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you, or (d) where the collection and processing of the personal information is in our or a third-party’s legitimate interests, which shall not be overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms.
Where we rely on your consent to process the personal information, you have the right to withdraw or decline your consent at any time.  The withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of the processing based on consent prior to its withdrawal.
Should you have additional questions or require further clarification concerning the legal basis for which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us at privacy@bluetie.com.
15. Privacy Policy Changes
If we decide to materially change our privacy policy for BlueTie, we will prominently post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.
16. Whom to Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact BlueTie at:
Privacy Policy
BlueTie, Inc.
120 Allens Creek
STE 220
Rochester, NY 14618
Or, you may contact us by email: privacy@bluetie.com
